forestriverinc.com 2011-11-30

# 

## Forest River, Inc. Web Site Privacy Policy

Forest River, Inc. and its affiliated companies value the privacy of each user who visits our websites. Forest River, Inc. has adopted this Web Site Privacy Policy ("Policy") to memorialize Forest River, Inc.'s current data collection and disclosure policies and practices for this web site and its related web pages (the "Site"). 

## Consent

By using the Site, you consent to this Policy. If you do not consent to this Policy, please refrain from use of the Site. All information gathered from the Site will be stored and processed in the United States. If you access the Site from a location other than the United States, your use of the Site constitutes consent to the transfer of your information to the United States. 

## Collection of Information

Forest River, Inc. may collect personally identifiable information from users at certain locations on the Site (such as your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, or credit card information for online purchases). Forest River, Inc. also collects non-personal and anonymous information from users to be used in an aggregate fashion. For example, Forest River, Inc. may collect system-related information, such as an IP address, browser type and operating system type to be used for system administration purposes, to help diagnose problems with our servers, to monitor traffic patterns, to determine which services are used most frequently and to assess site usage. Forest River, Inc. may retain information we gather about you indefinitely. 

This Site may contain links to other web sites. Forest River, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of web sites not owned by Forest River, Inc. that you may link to or may be linked from this Site. We encourage you to review the privacy policies and terms and conditions of such web sites so that you understand how those companies collect, use and share your information. This Policy applies solely to the information that Forest River, Inc. collects on this Site and does not apply to information Forest River, Inc. may collect by any alternative means or media. 

## Use of Information

Generally, Forest River, Inc. uses the information it gathers to operate and improve the Site and Forest River, Inc.'s services, to create a positive user experience, and to deliver various products and services we offer. We may also use information we gather to inform you of new products or services available or under consideration, technical issues, customer satisfaction surveys or account updates and related purposes. Except as otherwise provided in this Policy, Forest River, Inc. presently does not intend to sell, rent or provide access to your personally identifiable information to third parties that are not affiliated with Forest River, Inc., but reserves the right to do so in its sole discretion and without notice or compensation to you, unless prohibited by applicable law. 

## Disclosure of Information

Forest River, Inc. may disclose personally identifiable and aggregate anonymous information to companies and individuals hired to perform functions on our behalf. These companies and individuals may have access to your personal information to perform their functions. 

If one of Forest River, Inc.'s business lines or the entire business, or a substantial portion thereof, is acquired or transferred, whether by merger, consolidation or purchase of a substantial portion of assets, Forest River, Inc. may disclose and transfer your personally identifiable information to such third party acquiring Forest River, Inc.. In addition, if Forest River, Inc. becomes the subject of a bankruptcy or insolvency proceeding, whether voluntary or involuntary, Forest River, Inc. or its trustee in bankruptcy may sell, assign, license or otherwise transfer such information in a transaction approved by the appropriate court. Forest River, Inc. may also disclose your personal information to third parties when we believe, in good faith and in our sole discretion, that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) enforce or apply the terms and conditions of this Site; (b) comply with legal or regulatory requirements; (c) protect the rights, property or safety of Forest River, Inc., our users or other third parties; or (d) prevent a crime or protect national security. 

Forest River, Inc. may disclose aggregate anonymous information to its clients, business partners, merchants, advertisers, potential advertisers, investors, potential buyers and other third parties if Forest River, Inc. deems such disclosure, in its sole discretion, to have sound business reasons or justification. 

When you access or use Forest River, Inc. services or the Site through any co-branded web sites or linked web pages, your personal information may be disclosed to and become the property of both Forest River, Inc. and the relevant co-sponsor. In that case, the use of your personally identifiable information by the co-sponsor company will be subject to the privacy policy of that company, and Forest River, Inc. is not responsible for nor subject to the co-sponsor's policy regarding their use of your personally identifiable information. Accordingly, we encourage you to review the privacy policies and practices of any relevant co-sponsor before supplying any personal information. 

## Cookies

Forest River, Inc. may use "cookies" for the convenience of our users and to enhance your experience using the Site. A cookie is a small text file that is recorded either temporarily or persistently on your hard drive by a web page server and is not used to deliver viruses or other harmful programs to your computer. Rather, cookies enable Forest River, Inc. to recognize a user without requiring the user to repeatedly log in when using the Site or other Forest River, Inc. web sites. By relying on cookies, Forest River, Inc. is able to deliver a more efficient service that is more personalized for each user. Additionally, cookies allow Forest River, Inc. to monitor traffic patterns and Site usage which help make the Site more useful. 

Most browsers automatically accept cookies. If you prefer, you generally have the option of setting your browser to decline cookies. Alternatively, you may be able to modify your browser setting to notify you each time a cookie is created and permit you to accept or decline cookies on an individual basis or to accept cookies from web sites that meet certain disclosure and use specifications. 

## Children 

The Site is not intended for children. Forest River, Inc. does not knowingly or specifically collect personal information from users under 18 years of age. In the event that Forest River, Inc. becomes aware that it has collected personal information from a user under 18 years of age, it will take steps to delete such information from its database. Forest River, Inc. does not authorize users under 18 years of age to use the Site or Forest River, Inc. services. 

## Policy Changes

Forest River, Inc. may change this Policy at any time. In particular, Forest River, Inc. may modify this Policy to reflect changes in the way we collect, use or disclose information or to reflect changes in privacy laws, regulations and/or industry standards. We encourage you to review this Policy when accessing the Site. Continued use of the Site following changes indicates your acceptance of the changes. 

## Applicable Law

This Policy shall be governed by the laws of the State of Indiana, without regard to conflicts of law principles, and exclusive jurisdiction and venue for any dispute arising out of this Policy shall be the state court or district federal court for Elkhart, Indiana.
